dramavid.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy|Dramavid

Privacy Policy for www.dramavid.com  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our  
privacy policy, please feel to contact us by Email: dramasvid@gmail.com  
At www.dramavid.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme  
importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of  
personal information is received and collected by  
www.dramavid.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.dramavid.com makes use of log  
files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (  
IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ),  
date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to  
analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around  
the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and  
other such information are not linked to any information that is  
personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.dramavid.com does not use cookies.

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
Google or any other third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads  
on www.dramavid.com.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users  
based on their visit to www.dramavid.com and other sites on the  
Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the  
Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL –  
<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons  
on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

Google Adsense

Chitika

Amazon

infolinks

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the  
advertisements and links that appear on www.dramavid.com send  
directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP  
address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies,  
JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party  
ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements  
and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.dramavid.com has no access to or control over these  
cookies that are used by third-party advertisers

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third -

party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as  
well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  
www.dramavid.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we  
cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual  
browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
